



poneill759@gmail.com



@pearsdsgn



@pearse_oneill

-About Me —

Hi! I'm Pearse and I'm a 20 year old Graphic Designer based in Belfast. I am currently studying Interaction Design at the Belfast School of Art.

I have a great love for all things visual. My main passion is branding but I also love to utilise my design skills on web design, prototyping, digital art and illustration.

I'm a very outgoing character with a lot of experience in team work which drives my love for working with others.

Experience

Freelance Work

I have been doing freelance design work since I was in secondary school, majoritively branding work.

Pixel Pioneers, Volunteer (2017)

Responsibilities included manning the registration desk, distributing flyers and goodie bags & Q&A mic running.

Bubbacue, Front of House (2016-Present)

Duties included delivering a high standard of customer service on the tills, preparing food & working as part of a team. I was also involved in creating graphics and setting up photographs for promotional social media posts.

Giuseppe's, Pizza Chef (2014-2016)

I started out as a dishwasher and worked my way up by doing food prep then moving onto till work and eventually becoming a fully fledged pizza chef.



Education

Christian Brothers Grammar School, Omagh (2008-2015)

10 GCSEs achieved grade A*-A 3 A Levels in Art, History & ICT grade AAB.

Belfast School of Art (2015-2019)

BA (Hons) Art & Design (Foundation Year for Specialist Degrees), Distinction achieved.

BDes (Hons) Interaction Design, due to graduate in 2019.



Skills 4









Branding

Paper Prototyping

Idea Generation

HTML5, CSS & Javascript

Software Skills













Hobbies & Interests







Travel

Photography

Music







Crosswords

References -

Rachel Johnston Manager, Bubbacue +44 7772 768644 rachel@bubbacue.com

Paul McCormack Course Director, Interaction Design, Ulster University p.mccormack@ulster.ac.uk